

# contact@johnevanofski.net

720 938 4999

Oakland, Bay Area CA http://johnevanofski.net

### BIO

John Evanofski is a Bay Area web developer and designer with a diverse technological skillset and a problem solving aptitude. He is also an adept communicator and an experienced technology educator. His goal is to use his skills to bridge the gap between the user and the designer in order to continue the tradition of good design.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Web and Graphic Design Lead Clean LED Energy / Oakland CA / 2014

Web Developer and General Tech Support YogaKula / Berkeley CA / 2012-2014

Independent Web and Graphic Design
David Kerr Designs / Oakland CA / 2012-2014
Cindy Cleary Art / 2014
Mission Creek Festival / Oakland CA / 2013
SJ Sallinger Designs / San Francisco CA / 2013

### Teaching

HTML & CSS, Computing / Tutor / Wyzant.com / 2014 WordPress / AcademyX / 2013 Excel '98 & 2010 / ServiceSource Inc / 2009-2013

## SKILLS

#### WEB

- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP
- Ruby
- Responsive Web
- WordPress CMS

## ADOBE CREATIVE SUITE

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- Fireworks
- Dreamweaver

#### **OTHER**

- Final Cut Pro
- Ableton Live
- Microsoft Office Suite

#### EDUCATION

Liberal Arts Humanities (AA)
Digital Art Certificate
City College San Francisco / 2013

Web Design Certificate
AcademyX / 2011

